

PROFILE

I am a software Engineer passionate about technology with 3 years of experience in front-end development with Angular and reactive programming with rxjs. I focus on web technologies and development best practices.

Throughout my carreer path I have acquired knowledge in Typescript, javascript, Angular, React, css, HTML, sass, Angular Material, Boostrap and rxjs. Experienced on team work using SCRUM methodology, azure and implementing practices like daily, planning, grooming and retrospective.

CONTACT

- alexandercordoba.dev@ gmail.com
- 318-408-3717

REFERENCES

CESAR DARIO CORDOBA

Ing. Electrónico cel. 3152351239 Bogotá-Colombia

YADY MILENA JIMENEZ

Ing. biomedica cel. 3163808137 Popayan-Colombia

EDUCATION

University Corporation Autónoma of cauca

2020 Graduated with honors from the Autonoma University of Cauca.

WORK EXPERIENCE

University Autónoma of cauca

MAR 2019 - AGO 2019

• I developed 3 software in angular 6 and Firebase together with the university seedbed. These softwares were registered in the national direction of copyright.

SITIS – Soluciones Informáticas Integrales en Salud S.A.S

NOV 2019 - JUL 2020

• Frontend developer with Angular 10 and reactive programming with rxjs for hospital software.

Asesoftware

JUL 2020 - Present

• Intermediate Frontend Developer with Angular, rxjs, angular material, boostrap, typescript and scss .

SKILLS

- I have advanced knowledge in Javascript and typescript and intermediate knowledge in React.
- I master technologies like HTML, CSS and SCSS.
- I have advanced knowledge in Bootstrap and material design.
- I have knowledge in ionic with capacitor and angular.
- I adapt well to collaborative work with technologies such as git, github, jira and azure.